好了  小伙子
Okay, buddy--
女同胞们都去露营了
Womenfolk are out camping.
老爹去打高尔夫了
Dad is out golfing.
这就意味着我们有一整天
And that means we have all day
来为所欲为了
To do whatever we want.
早就意识到了  哥们
Way ahead of you, dude.
不然我怎么会用脚来吃排骨呢
Why do you think I'm eating a rib with my foot?
简直让我印象深刻啊
As impressed with that as I am...
我有更大的计划
I've got bigger plans.
你是指用脚吃鸡腿么
You mean like eating a drumstick with my foot.
得了吧  伙计  我说的是
Okay, buddy, I am talking about
一个赚一大笔外快的好方法
A way to make cold, hard cash.
你抓住了我的注意力
You have my full attention.
别把这机会浪费了
Don't waste this moment.
丽芙·鲁尼住宅游
Liv Rooney residential tour--
只花一小笔钱  当地的《放声歌唱》粉丝俱乐部的成员们
For a small fee, members of the local "sing it loud!" fan club
就可以看到他们最爱的青少年偶像
Can see where their favorite teen idol
生活起居的地方
Eats, sleeps, and obsessively flosses.
我一直在收集她的用完的洗发水瓶子
I've been collecting her empty shampoo bottles
和剪下来的脚趾甲
And toenail clippings.
你能再搞个礼品店么
Can you say "gift shop"?
我就知道靠你这点精灵古怪
I knew i'd cash in on how creepy you were
能赚大钱
One of these days.
把你脚上的酱汁擦干净
Wipe that sauce off your foot.
住宅游再过一小时就开始了
The tour shows up in an hour.
嘿 同志们
Hey, guys.
高尔夫泡汤了
Golf got canceled.
真是倒霉催了
Bummer for me.
但是我们能一起度过这周末了
But we get to spend the weekend together now
享受一下父子增进感情的好时间
For a little father-son bonding time.
太好了
Yay.